{
  "posts": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "json-server",
      "author": "typicode"
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "First Question",
      "answer": "Is pretty lame",
      "chapter": "Chapter 5",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bac",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "what's your question",
      "answer": "this is for the Gene book",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "1",
      "answer": "2",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Chapter 1",
      "question": "What plant did Mendel use?",
      "answer": "Peas!",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bac",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Chapter 8",
      "question": "What is an allele",
      "answer": "It is a variant of the same gene. ",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bac",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Chapter 1",
      "question": "What should I do with my f**ks",
      "answer": "Allocate your f**ks accordingly",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bad",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Chapter 2",
      "question": "Is anything subtle",
      "answer": "Nothing.",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bad",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Chapter 1",
      "question": "Who's a spy",
      "answer": "me!",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bae",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Chapter 2",
      "question": "Who's the *other* spy?",
      "answer": "Also me!",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bae",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Minute 7",
      "question": "What happened to Chinese laborers after the railroads they build in the 1880s became profitable?",
      "answer": "The Chinese Exclusion Act of 1882 was passed that barred Chinese laborers to come into the country",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0baf",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Minute 8",
      "question": "What was the Immigration Act of 1924",
      "answer": "It barred all immigrants outside of the Wester hemisphere from becoming citizens. The US still needed Mexcian workers though, so that's why the Western hemisphere was excluded. They even aded a 2% max quote",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0baf",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Minute 10",
      "question": "What was the definition of \"White\" to gain citizenship?",
      "answer": "In 1922, a Japanese man went to the Supreme Court to gain Citizenship for his character, but the court said no, \"White\" = Caucasian. One year later, an Indian man (Indians considered Caucasian at the time), was denied citixenship because they said white is white skin -- we know it when we see it",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0baf",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Plenary Power Doctrine",
      "answer": "When the president and congress act they have full power over questions on immigration and questions of naturalization. ",
      "chapter": "Minute16",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0baf",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Minute 20: Implicit Bias",
      "question": "What are the two kinds of bias?",
      "answer": "Implicit and Explicit. Implicit Bias - tou basically \"hashtag\" a person with a race/age/etc; then you associate all the prior things you hashtagged with that person. You are unaware of these, may not be endorsed. You are not able to self report the data to support these. Explicit bias is based on real prior experineces.",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0baf",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Minute 26: Implicit Bias",
      "question": "What is the Implicit Association Test (IAT)",
      "answer": "Measures time delta when positive and negative words are associated with pictures of different race'd people",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0baf",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Mintute 35",
      "question": "What is a Pearson's correlation (r value) and what was it's value for Implicit Bias",
      "answer": "It defines the correlation [-1,1] of two things. The value is 0.23 for Implicit bias, which is statistically insignificant, yet other things like smoking to lung cancer (r=0.08) and lead paint with IQ deficiency (r=0.12) are far lower... think about that...",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0baf",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "chapter": "Minute 1",
      "question": "Who is Elizabeth Eckford",
      "answer": "She was one of the first black students ever to attend classes at Little Rock Central High School in Little Rock, Arkansas",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bb0",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "chapter": "The Fear of Engagement Video",
      "question": "What is red lining?",
      "answer": "It was a legal practice where banks would draw lines around poor neighborhoods (disproportionately black) and regardless of credit, the people there would not be given loans. These areas are thus devoid of capital to improve the community",
      "readableId": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bb0",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 18
    }
  ],
  "readables": [
    {
      "title": "The Gene",
      "description": "An Intimate History",
      "type": "book",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "title": "The Subtle Art",
      "description": "of Not Giving a Fuck(s) plural",
      "type": "book",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "title": "Expats",
      "description": "The story about a bunch of spys",
      "type": "Book",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "title": "History of Racism in the US",
      "description": "Amazon CORE video (1)",
      "type": "Video",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 4,
      "_id": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0baf"
    },
    {
      "title": "History of Racism in the US Educational System",
      "description": "Amazon CORE 2018 - Race & Exclusion in American Education",
      "type": "Amazon Broadcast video",
      "creatorId": "111052686678665904773",
      "id": 5,
      "_id": "5ef015fc7dd0b674f4ac0bb0"
    }
  ],
  "comments": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "body": "some comment",
      "postId": 1
    }
  ],
  "profile": {
    "name": "typicode"
  }
}